You too have already assimilated You are almost
Вы же тоже ассимилировать уже Вы почти
Russian there you do not know your language
русские там вы языка своего не знаете
in Russian You speak the same Well here it is
по-русски Говорите тоже Ну тут это уже
no longer worth saying assimilate
не стоит говорить ассимилировать
assimilate for example again there for
ассимилировать к примеру опять же там к
example not meant KK your yes that is yes
примеру не во виду КК ваша да то есть да
Chuvash They have already more even more
чуваш Они уже больше ещё больше
assimilated yes yes And the Tatars do not have everything
ассимилировать да да А у татар нет всё
Well how Look I looked there are
Ну как Смотри я вот смотрел там
Azerbaijanis these Kazakhs they are also Turks
азербайджанцы эти казахи они же тоже
Yes they Yes but they came from the
тюрки Да они Да но они вышли из
Soviet Union and they have an
Советского Союза и у них там есть
Azerbaijani language there songs everything there is in the
азербайджанский язык песень всё там на
national Kazakh as well and the Tatars VS
национальном казахе также а татары ВС
they already ruet
они рует уже
Rus Hello Lezgins Hello No it's not
русе Привет лезгины Приве Нет это не
Lezgin Zhek And what Tatar and Tatar I
лезгинский Жек А какой татарский а
understood I'm a little confused Yes you are
татарский понял Я немножко путаю Да вы
from Tatarstan specifically Yes I understood and the World Cup you
из Татарстана именно Да понял а ЧМ
communicate
общаетесь
Tatars about VSM Dani about the World Cup look at what
татары обо всм Дани о ЧМ смот какой
interlocutors I just communicate in
собеседников Я как раз общаюсь на
different nationalities in the Russian
национальностей разных в Российской
Federation my father is Chuvash
Федерации у меня отец он чуваш
himself not far from
сам недалеко от
Tatarstan And my mother
Татарстана А мама
Bashkir so well,
башкирка так что
under the Soviet Union, they came to
ну При Советском Союзе они ещё приехали
Ukraine to study in Kharkov and
в Украину в Харьков учиться и тут
met here and stayed and then
познакомились тут остались а потом
Ukraine separated and stayed to
Украина Ну отделилась и уже так остались
live here Not bad Not bad Not bad and do you
жить тут Неплохо Неплохо Неплохо а вы
know the Tatar language they study you now
язык татарский знаете вас изучают сечас
of course everything is in two languages ​​with us
конечно у нас всё везде на двух языках
everything is mandatory And how is
всё обязательно А как как хлеб
Tatar bread and Freedom and
татарский а Свобода а
Irek Irek Irek understood
Ирек Ирек Ирек понял
cool I don't know you don't speak Well, my
прикольно Я не знаю не владеешь Да ну я
father is Chuvash My mother is Bashkort they
у меня отец чуваш Мама башкорт они
spoke Russian to me because
по-русски со мной говорили потому что ну
well, in Ukraine neither Chuvash nor Bashkor was
как бы в Украине ни чувашский ни башкор
needed not Barsky Bashkir
ский не нужен был не Барский башкирский
not Barsky
у не Барский
Bashkor itself on Bashkort as if well, I do
башкор само на башкорт как бы ну я в том
n't look at that, it was the Russians who called them Bashkirs Well, yes, Bashkor Bashkor
не смотри это русские назвали башкиры Ну
yes Bashkor just like, for
да башкор башкор да башкор так же как
example, Russians say Kyrgyz and not
например русские говорят киргизы а не
there Kyrgyz and Kyrgyzstan and not
там кыргызы да Кыргызстан а не
Kyrgyzstan Russians They call in their own way
Киргизия русские Они по-своему называют
there always in short well, yes, everywhere It
там всегда короче ну да везде Мне
seems to me so  And by the way, how is it going there?
кажется так А у вас там кстати как
Listen, it's a sin to complain about what you do in
нормак Слушай грех жаловаться на самом
life,
Чем по жизни занимаетесь
training, sports,
тренировки спорт
Oh, what kind of sportsman is this? Army hand-to-hand
О что за спортик Армейский рукопашный
combat, Cool, I'm also a hand-to-hand combat trainer, Oh, Not bad,
бой Прикольно я тоже рукопашным я тренер
not bad, children at
о Неплохо неплохо детей на
competitions in Ukraine are
соревнования в Украине
different. And you, like, you
отличается А вы вы типа там с наживой
also do a fight with profit, army
бой тоже делаете армейский
hand, only a sports discipline, I understand, fight, fight, fight, fight, stop, stop, no
рукой только спортивная дисциплина я
throws, why is it not the case with throws, look, there are their own
бросками не дело в том что смотри всюду
Federations there, they can make their own, in short, there are
там свои Федерации могут делать свои
rules, you have throws, and
короче там правила у вас броски есть а
wrestling on the tatami, there are also, yes, of course, yes. Well, I
борьба на татами Есть тоже да конечно да
understand everything, that is, in short, in essence,
А ну всё понял то есть короче по сути
it's like combat [ __ ] with cops,
это как боевое самбо ментами
Xin, well,
ксин ну
that's an interesting question. I looked at what
такой вот интересный вопрос я смотрел
you have in Russia now, some kind of
что сейчас там в России у вас какая-то
Russian organization, the Russian
есть такая русская организация русская
community, I heard that they gather there
община слышал с они типа там собираются
and they load all
и типа грузят всех
non-Russians, no, there's no
нерусских нет тамм
time, in Moscow, and
вре в Моск и я
sometimes I saw the Kyrgyz people, I
виде порой киргизы у нацию ничего
can't
плохого не могу
say anything bad about the nation, fact. What we saw,
сказать фак Что видели то
we saw, they speak out directly against
видели выступают непосредственно против
lawlessness, because it
беспредела потому что
happens in Tatarstan.  there Islam Yes Tatars are
бывает в Татарстане там Ислам Да татары
Muslims majority and many Russians are
мусульмане большинство и многие русские
just against having mosques there
как раз против того чтобы там мечети
they want to build churches there in
были они хотят церкви ставить там в
Tatarstan so that mosques are not built in Moscow
Татарстане чтобы в Москве не ставили
how do you feel about this listen you
мечети как ты к этому относишься слушай
know as a Muslim of course I don't have a
знаешь как как мусульманин конечно не
very good attitude to the Cabinet of Ministers but again let's
очень хорошо КМУ отношусь но опять же
repeat I live in Tatarstan and we don't have
повторимся я живу в Татарстане и у нас
such a problem and what, let's say, is
такой проблемы нету а то что ну скажем
happening at the neighbor doesn't
так происходит у соседе не так сильно
bother me so much just so that the network and
волнует меня вот пря так чтобы сеть и
think in fact that is we have a lot
думать на самом деле то есть у нас много
and a lot of mosques and churches as if the people
и мечети много и церквей как бы народ
live in harmony That is how everyone is
живёт дружно То есть как всё всех
happy with everything everyone is
устраивает все прекрасно
moving
двигаются
along great not in this regard Tatarstan is a
прикольно не в этом плане Татарстан
very interesting republic there are many Nations
очень интересная республика много Наций
Everyone lives as kindly as possible there is a
Все живут максимально добро у те
bell right there there is an Azan will be
и колокол тут же те Азан будет
enough Great to say in a good
достаточно Здорово сказать в хорошем
way Union 2.0 that is about that Well and for
плане Союз 2.0 то есть о ту Ну а
example do I understand correctly that you do
Например я правильно понимаю что у вас
n't have a flag of the Russian Federation but you have a
нету флага Российской Федерации но есть
flag of Tatarstan Yes you
флаг Татарстана
mean in the
Да имеешь в виду в
sense Well you say you have you
смысле Ну ты говоришь У вас есть имеешь
mean in stock or I or in general
в виду в наличи или у меня или вообще у
you have no I have only
тебя Да нет у меня талько
Tatarstan understood correctly not to
Татарстана понял правильно не русский
hold the Russian flag No I will not do anything about the
флаг держать Нет я ничего не буду про
Russian flag Well here it's just well
русский флаг Ну тут просто ну
I want to have a flag of Tatarstan let's say so that
мне хочется иметь флаг таста скажем так
is I am aggressively inclined towards the
то есть я агрессивно настроен в сторону
Russian flag there I am not short come the
там русского флага меня не корот приди
Ukrainian
украинского
flag maximally ska maximally kind
флага максимально ска максимально добрый
loyal to
лояльный
everyone that in principle I think is right
всем что в принципе я считаю правильно
Why do you not have Chuvash
Почему у тебя не чувашского
there is some kind of
есть же какая-то там са
self-identity self-identification Well well
самоидентичность самоидентификация Да ну
as if I do not have a community here neither Chuvash
как бы я тут не имею общины ни Чувашской
nor Bashkor so I already as if to
ни башкор ской поэтому я уже как бы
assimilate already You are almost Russian there you do
ассимилировать уже Вы почти русские там
not know your language in Russian You
вы языка своего не знаете по-русски
also speak Well here it is no longer worth
Говорите тоже Ну тут это уже не стоит
saying assimilate assimilate for
говорить ассимилировать ассимилировать к
example again there for example No
примеру опять же там к примеру Не в
offense to KK Chuvashih yes that is yes Chuvashi They are
обиду КК чувашах да то есть да чуваш Они
already more even more
уже больше ещё больше
like Look I looked there
как Смотри я вот смотрел там
Azerbaijanis these Kazakhs they are also Turks Yes
азербайджанцы эти казахи они же тоже
they Yes but they came from the
тюрки Да они Да но они вышли из
Soviet Union they have an
Советского Союза у них там есть
Azerbaijani language there songs Everything is shorter
азербайджанский язык песень Всё короче
there in the national Kazakh  also and
там на национальном казахе также а
Tatars all they are Russes already Russes Well it's like
татары всё они русе уже русе Ну это как
with us please you walk around the city with
у нас пожалуйста ты гуляя по городу у
us everything is everywhere in two languages ​​everything is everywhere
нас всё везде на двух языках всё везде
metro names of streets in stores in schools
метро название улиц в магазинах в школах
Well in schools in schools in schools in schools they teach math
Да ну в школах в школах математику учат
there in Russ really Why are there Tatar
там русм правда Почему есть татарские
schools there is something there somewhere a little bit
школы есть что-то там где-то немножко
it's not something somewhere it is And that's
это не что-то где-то это есть И этого
enough that is
достаточно то есть
here here like well here I have
здесь вот здесь как бы ну здесь у меня я
Lada still more information
Ладе всё-таки больше информации
agree Agree Let's go now I'll
согласитесь Согласись Давай сейчас я
go and open the website of the Republic of Tatarstan
зайду и открою сайт Республики Татарстан
and see if it is conducted in two languages
и посмотрю ли он на двух языках ведётся
Let's do it
Давай
now like this now it's
сейчас так сейчас
just interesting or the
просто интересно или администрация
city administration city council of the city of Kazan Yes
города городской совет города Казань Да
Check here the Kazan City Duma
Проверяй вот Казанская городская Дума
kzn.ru does
kzn.ru
not let me on this site
так не пускает меня на этот сайт
now because what is it called with you
сейчас так как как у вас называется
it does not find it But the official
что-то она не находит её А вот офици
mayor's office of Kazan
мэрия Казани кзн
kzn.ru does not give access to this site ok
ру не даёт доступ к этому сайту хорошо
No I'm telling you everything it is everywhere
Нет я тебе говорю всё оно везде
in the bank you can choose
есть в банке ты можешь выбрать
service in Tatar or in Russian
обслуживание на татарском или на русском
but this is not in all banks  Bank Bars You
но это не во всех ба банка Барс Ты
can call to say in Tatar I
можешь позвонить сказать на татарском
want you to be transferred to the operator who
хочу тебя переведут на оператора который
Vlad Tarsky I am in the hall now he goes in
Владе тарским я зал на сейчас заходит
opens the website of the government of the Republic of
открывает сайт правительства республики
Tatarstan now we will open
Татарстан сейчас мы откроем
and does not want to release you see under the
и не хочет выпускать видишь под
pins Well this is already a waste of time as if no longer not just
пинами Ну это уже трата времени как бы
I look Google
уже не не просто я смотрю Google
shows that it is in Russian Now I will open it
показывает что он на русском Сейчас я
no There you can choose
его открою нет Там же ты можешь выбрать
Russian or I want Yes I want to look I want to open
русский или хочу Да я хочу посмотреть Я
what is just interesting
хочу открыть что просто интересно
news is filled in Tatar also in
новости наполняются на татарском тоже
parallel or only in
параллельно или только на
[music]
[музыка]
Russian and you can just go because
русском а можешь зайти просто потому что
I can see from Ukraine does not open it
у меня видно из Украины не открывает его
can so that your colleague
можешь чтобы с телефона твой коллега
opened it from the phone and looked If on the
открыл его и посмотрел Если на
government website in Tatar
сайте правительство на татарском
Yes there you go please
Да вот те пожалуйста
dial right right away
набери
here per right right
сразу вот пер правильно правильно
here Show what
вот Покажи что
nar Rustam
нар Рустам
Tulin Well what do you have there would
Тулин Ну что там у тебя б
not release or what [ __ ] now he
же не выпускал что ли бля сейчас он тебе
will show you but no In fact here is the
покажет но нет На самом
phone
телефона
Here press
Вот нажми
Tatar and show
татарский и покажи
[music]
[музыка]
Yes no what document Well damn
Да нет документ какой Ну блин
yes
да
now the official
сейчас официальный
portal is
портал
Tatar e the menu will be in Tatar
татарский е менюшка будет на татарском
maybe that's all  now I'll take a picture
может и всё сейчас я сфотографирую
just show from the phone some kind of crap
просто покажу с телефона какая-то фигня
turns out it
получается плохо
loads poorly that
прогружается то
is I think it will be visible here is the site itself
есть я думаю будет видно вот сам сайт
wait ses I don't see it's not visible how much
подожди сес Я не вижу не видно сколько
will be
будет
visible well
видно
in what language
ну на каком язы
so domain Yes this is a menu menu A go to the
так домен Да это менюшка менюшка А зайди
news itself Yes of course the
новость Да конечно
news as well As you
новость также
can see on vi Show me here is the
Как видишь на ви Покажи мне вот
Constitution of the Republic of Tatarstan in
Конституция Республика Татарстан на
Tatar
татарском
yoshi bend Well so there well on the
ёши гнуть Ну так там ну на сайте
government website there should
правительства должен
be need to
быть нужно
search ask a question service contacts
искать задать вопрос служба контакты
government A well here is an
правительство А ну вот
interest in the language will speak uh the official
интерес языке будет говорить э чиновник
in Russian or in Tatar m Listen this
на русском или на татарском м Слушай это
now I have to search very hard no no right you
сейчас меня искать очень сильно не не
need to go from the phone Look in
вот прямо надо с телефона Посмотри в
any news where there is a video Well
любой новости где там видео Ну вот
look I went for example biography here
смотри я зашёл к примеру биография тут
people in Tatar there are eight Well this is a
людей на татарском есть восьми Ну это
biography this was filled out documents
биография это наполнили документы
wait documents in Tatar take a
подожди документы на татарском возьми
video really now we will hear
видео вот реально вот сейчас мы услышим
yes What language do they speak on the video in
да На каком языке говорят на видео на
Tatar or on this government where are
татарском или на это правительстве где
they here we have a press service
они здесь у нас пресс-служба
video reports so well twenty fifth
видеорепортажи так ну двадцать пятый
year So turn on the video and that's it I watch Well
год Так включи видео и всё я смотрю Ну
in Russian here  they
на русском здесь
say Well, I do
говорят Да ну в Я ничего такого как бы
n't see anything like that here they speak Russian well
не вижу здесь говорят на русском ну
please Not everyone knows in Tatarstan
пожалуйста Не все же знают в Татарстане
Well, the Tatar language that not only everything, that
Ну татарский язык что не только всё то
is, everything, that is, they say everything in Russian That's what
есть всё то есть на русском говорят всё
I wanted to
Вот это я хотел
hear, like, that is, an infringement
услышать как бы то есть ущемление
really, like there is none there, they
реально как такого там его нету нас-то
did something to us that being in the
сделали что там находясь в Думе
Tatar Duma you can both Well, in Russian and
татарской ты можешь как Ну и на русском
in Tatar, express this, there is
так и на татарском излагать это есть
freedom Well, that's it If you
свобода Ну вот так вот Если
figure it out, I understand Listen, I have a
разобраться понял Слушай у меня же
question, there was such an actor, not an actor, but a
вопрос есть был такой актёр не актёр а
singer, DZO, he
певец дзо выступает
also performs I know that there is such an actor, he is there,
ещё я знаю что есть такой актёр он там
Sval Pavuk In short, I don't know something else I don't
свал павук Короче что-то ещё не вкурсе
watch Well, I don't listen I'm not a fan of music at all I understand I
не смотрю Ну не слушаю Я вообще не фанат
understand Well, in principle, I think
музыки понял понял Ну в принципе думаю
everything Thank you for an interesting dialogue
всё спасибо тебе за интересный диалог
Thank you Good luck to you, all the
Благодарю тебя Удачи тебе все самого
best,
хорошего
say it in Tatar sa I told you
скажи это по-татарски са Я тебе сказал
just not here is the phrase completely just sa
просто не вот фразу полностью просто са
everything everything that's all a
всё
letter to y instag I don't know
всё вот и всё пись на й instag Я не знаю
why this is for what tob there to
для чого це тоб для чого тоб там
watch on otse y face But for you this is
дивитись на оце й фейс Але для тебе це
one  two or three clicks But you try
один два або три клика Але ты тримае
me and I will be like in me there are a bunch of fouls
мене и я буду каза в мене там Купа фолов
and in me there will be a cool mood to make
и в мене буде класный настр чтоб робити
new cool videos Write to my Instagram
нове крут видео Пиши на мий Instagram
Popik Andriy
Попик Андрий
then Come on I'll chka
отак Давай я чка